# Giordano Bruno B. B. Silva

São Luís, Maranhão, Brazil



giordanosi2011@gmail.com



+5594992897744



linkedin.com/in/giordano-bruno-silva



https://giordano.dev.br/

# Summary

Hardworking and self-motivated web developer with 4+ years of experience. Solid knowledge in JavaScript development, from backend applications with Node to frontend with well-known libraries and frameworks such as Angular and React. Basic experience with Java, C/C++ and Python languages, but always willing to deepen knowledge in any area. Able to work collaborating with a team, or even self-managing independent projects.

# **Experience**



### Backend Developer

Wipro

Oct 2021 - Present (5 months +)

- Development and maintenance of Node services, ensuring scalability and availability of customer services. Currently working for Bradesco bank.



## IT Technician

Instituto Brasileiro do Meio Ambiente e dos Recursos Naturais Renováveis - IBAMA Jan 2021 - Sep 2021 (9 months)

- Performed help desk activities for civil servants.
- Performed maintenance and configuration of network equipments, operational systems (Windows and Linux), and computers.



#### Fullstack Engineer

Devplus Desenvolvimento de Software

Feb 2020 - Jan 2021 (1 year)

- Planned and built a PWA system from scratch, for managing loyalty cards for a hospital. The technologies used were Angular, Node and Typescript. The backend today has more than 5000 registered patients.
- Built more than 20 websites with Wordpress and Angular. Among these are an e-commerce for selling tour tickets, and a dropshipping e-commerce.



#### IT Technician

Instituto Brasileiro do Meio Ambiente e dos Recursos Naturais Renováveis - IBAMA Mar 2018 - Jul 2019 (1 year 5 months)

- Performed help desk activities for civil servants.
- Performed maintenance and configuration of network equipments, operational systems (Windows and Linux), and computers.



### **Fullstack Engineer**

Markteam Soluções para Web

Jun 2016 - Mar 2018 (1 year 10 months)

- Developed more than 20 websites using Wordpress, Joomla, PHP, Javascript and JQuery, for small and medium-sized companies, public agencies such as city halls and town councils.
- Performed social network management activities, creating posts, texts and promoting clients businesses.

### **Education**

Federal University of South and Southeast Pará

Bachelor of Information Technology, Information Technology Aug 2011 - Jun 2018

# **Licenses & Certifications**

Ignite ReactJS - Rocketseat 6f4c6659-7924-4a88-a412-3347ab740748

- gti Bootcamp Full Stack IGTI
- Scrum na Prática Federal University of South and Southeast Pará
- UI Design for Beginners Origamid c5308d8d
- **EF SET English Certificate 73/100 (C2 Proficient)** EF Standard English Test (EF SET)